SETH MARTINEAU

Cottonwood Heights, UT 84121

(801)884-7571 | seth.r.martineau@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sethmartineau/ | https://github.com/slothings | https://slothings.github.io/react-portfolio/#/react-portfolio/about

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Developer with an Economics background and Customer Service skills to incorporate into building logical and user-friendly applications. Recently graduated from a Full-Stack Web Development program through the University of Utah. Learning more about CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Node, React, and responsive web design every day. Known for being creative, I hope to bring my skills and approach to a team. With every project, I like to bring in my own interests and passions into it, making it more fun to work on and more impactful for myself and other people who share my interests. I have worked on a few applications that my friends and I have personally used, such as a gaming planner, and a trivia game based/themed on Among Us. Recently I have broadened my horizons by working on a video chat app for veterinarians called Get Pet Vet. I'm excited to bring my skills and ideas to a team and help build more applications.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

CSS, Express, Git, GitHub, Handlebars, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, MERN, MongoDB, Mongoose, MySQL, Node, React

PROJECTS

Get Pet Vet | https://github.com/slothings/get-pet-vet | https://evening-stream-63366.herokuapp.com/login

This application was born out of the idea to help the health of pets while decreasing the risk of COVID-19. Get Pet Vet allows users to create pet profiles, schedule an appointment, and lastly, have a video chat with a veterinarian. I mainly worked on creating pet profiles and viewing them, setting up databases and getting them to connect to our front end, getting our code integrated so it would work again, and lastly getting the video chat to function. This application was primarily built with BCrypt, CSS, ESLint, Passport.js, React, React Big Calendar, React Date Picker, Simple-Peer, Socket.io, and Travis Cl.

The Smartest Among Us | https://github.com/slothings/the-smartest-among-us | https://the-smartest-among-us | <a h

This application is a fun trivia game themed off of the popular app "Among Us." I mainly worked on the API, database setup and data retrieval, and getting login/signup authentication to work. This application was primarily built with BCrypt, CSS, ESLint, HTML, JavaScript, MySQL, Passport.js, and Travis Cl.

QR-Aid-Codes | https://github.com/slothings/qr-aid-codes | https://diegopie.github.io/QR-aid-Codes/

This application is a gaming scheduler using API's containing a massive gaming library and the option to create a QR code for the event created. I mainly worked on the JavaScript and incorporating the API's

into our app. This application was primarily built with Bulma CSS Framework, HTML, JavaScript and the API's used were rawg.io and qrickit.com.

EXPERIENCE

America First Credit Union | Loan Officer | March 2020 - July 2020

I would meet with members to determine their needs and recommend the right loan product to help meet their goals. I would maintain an active knowledge base of all the organization's loan products and the qualifications required of each applicant. I would review active loan files each day to determine is any documents were missing or needed to be finished to complete the members loan application. I would also utilize professional judgement to determine which potential borrowers represent good risk opportunities for the organization.

Log Haven | Event Coordinator | June 2019 - March 2020

I would consult with customers to determine objectives and requirements for events. I would review the event bill for accuracy and approve payment. I would confer with staff at a chosen event to coordinate details. I would monitor event activities to ensure compliance with applicable regulation and laws, satisfaction of participants, and resolution of any problems that arise. I would plan and develop programs, agendas, budgets, and services according to customer requirements and conduct post-event evaluations to determine how future events could be improved.

Verisys | Data Entry Specialist/Content Analyst | January 2019 - June 2019

I would document all investigative activities and prepare written reports and graphs of the findings. I would help analyze financial data to detect irregularities in areas such as billing trends, financial relationships, and regulatory compliance procedures. I would create and maintain logs, records, and databases of information about fraudulent activity and supply quality control necessary for regulatory submissions.

Wing Coop, LLC | Manager | June 2012 - December 2018

I would keep records required by the government agencies regarding sanitation or food subsidies and maintain food and equipment inventories and update their records. I would also schedule and receive food orders and check the contents to verify product quality and quantity. I would count the drawer and make bank deposits and establish the standard for personnel performance and customer service. I would schedule the staff hours and assign duties. I would also arrange the equipment maintenance and repairs and help resolve personnel problems, hire new staff, and evaluate employee performance.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development | Certificate | University of Utah

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Bootstrap, CSS3, Express, Handelbars.js, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, MongoDB, MySQL, Node Js, and ReactJS.

Economics | Bachelor of Science | University of Utah